{
  "categories": [],
  "description": " Guess what's missing in these famous pairs. ",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Pepper",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Salt & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Yang",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Yin & ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Queen",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "King & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "White",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Black & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Bow",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "___ & Arrow"
  }, {
    "answer": "Night",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "_____ & Day"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jelly",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Peanut Butter & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Cheese",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Macaroni & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lightning",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Thunder & _________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Needle",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "______ & Thread"
  }, {
    "answer": "Fish",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "____ & Chips"
  }, {
    "answer": "Pans",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Pots & ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Horse",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "_____ & Carriage"
  }, {
    "answer": "Nuts",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "____ & Bolts"
  }, {
    "answer": "Fauna",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Flora & _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Hammer",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "______ & Nails"
  }, {
    "answer": "Ladders",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Chutes & _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Tea",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "___ & Crumpets"
  }, {
    "answer": "Slow",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "____ & Steady"
  }, {
    "answer": "Carrots",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Peas & _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Leaps",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "_____ & Bounds"
  }, {
    "answer": "Rice",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Red Beans & ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Jetsam",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "Flotsam & ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Lamb",
    "category": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
    "question": "____ & Mint Jelly"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Things That Go Together Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/things-that-go-together-quiz.php"
}